

# **ARUNKUMAR B**

FLUTTER DEVOLPER

- Tholampalayam, Coimbatore
- barunkumar19@karunya.edu.in
- in linkedin.com/in/arun-kumar-cse

#### **PROFILE**

I am Arunkumar B . I am currently doing B.Tech Computer Science in Karunya Institute Of Technology And Sciences. Simultaneously I am working in hybrid devolpment (Flutter) which can be devolp for android , ios , desktop and website devolpment . I experience in programming skills such as C++ , java , dart etc. Additionally I am a good team player and a hard working person. I will never give up easily until the last I put my effort

#### **SKILLS**

C++

•••••

Mvsal

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ \circ$ 

Dart

•••••

Java

•••••

Python

•••••

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **FUTURE READY TALENT**

## Microsoft

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

This Internship is a virtual internship with an opportunity to learn the in-demand azure cloud & security skills aligned to industry needs. At end of this internship i had builded a portfolio site for a company. This project has hosted through Microsoft Azure.

#### JAVA CODING INTERNSHIP

# Suven Consultants and Technology Pvt.Ltd.

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021

I had made two projects under this coding internship using Java Swing in Java Programming . The projects that are completed during internship are listed below. Projects:

- 1. Consumer Loan Assistant Project
- 2. Home Inventory Manager Project

### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

## Karunya Institute of Technology and Sciences

Bachelor of Technology - BTech Computer Science and Engineering

2019 - 2023

# Metro Matriculation Higher Secondary School

Higher Secondary, Computer Science

2017 - 2019

## Sri Vinayaga Vidhyalaya Sr. Sec. School

Secondary

2017

# **PROJECTS**

**Land Probe Using Flutter** 

present

Simple Interest Calculator Using Flutter

Jan 2022 - Jan 2022